[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The octopus is considered the smartest invertebrate.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Tattoo is a wound. It oozes for a couple of days after it has been made. This is not recommended for you to do after you get a tattoo.", "correct_answer": "Swim and sunbathe", "incorrect_answers": ["Wash it soap", "Eat hot food", "Cover it with clothes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you have hyperthyroidism, your body is overproducing what hormone?", "correct_answer": "Thyroxine", "incorrect_answers": ["Estrogen", "Glucagon", "Thyrocalcitonin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who voiced Betty Boop also voiced Popeye.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the twin sons of Jesse and Becky from the Full House TV show?", "correct_answer": "Alex and Nicky", "incorrect_answers": ["Anthony and Darren", "Tony and T. J.", "Dave and Otis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cat was not referenced in the documentary Grey Gardens by either of the women?", "correct_answer": "Snowflake", "incorrect_answers": ["Whiskers", "Pinky", "Champion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you study calculus, you usually also study this branch of geometry.", "correct_answer": "Analytic geometry", "incorrect_answers": ["Bolyai geometry", "Discrete geometry", "Riemannian  geometry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Myorrhexis is a very painful condition and can occur when you overexert. What is characteristic of this condition?", "correct_answer": "Rupture or tearing of a muscle.", "incorrect_answers": ["Softening of a bone.", "A vertebra is out of its joint or is dislocated", "Degeneration of cartilage."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Lord of the Rings, what is Boromir\u2019s younger brother\u2019s name?", "correct_answer": "Faramir", "incorrect_answers": ["Haldir", "Albert", "Eomer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Women who wear their purse straps across their chests are at risk of being beheaded by purse snatchers.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name on Fogells fake ID in the comedy movie Superbad?", "correct_answer": "McLovin", "incorrect_answers": ["Sting", "Prince", "Muhammad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Mean Girls, what was the name of the academic club Ms. Norbury wanted Cady to join?", "correct_answer": "The Mathletes", "incorrect_answers": ["The Biomasters", "The English Assassins", "The Socialists"]}]